{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Jack was very tired ___ he was playing tennis all afternoon",
      "a": "as soon as",
      "b": "if",
      "c": "before",
      "d": "because",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Because: used when you are giving the reason for something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Linda often visited the China Town ___ I was staying in San Francisco.",
      "a": "while",
      "b": "until",
      "c": "throughout",
      "d": "during",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- While: during the time that something is happening",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is spring now, ___ the birds are singing.",
      "a": "because",
      "b": "though",
      "c": "for",
      "d": "unless",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- For: used to introduce the reason for something [= because] ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cows must eat grains, ___ they will not grow fat.",
      "a": "or",
      "b": "but",
      "c": "when",
      "d": "though",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- Or: used between two words or phrases to show that either of two things is possible\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have never spoken ill of him,___ I don't like him.",
      "a": "if",
      "b": "because",
      "c": "so that",
      "d": "though",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Though: used to introduce a statement that makes the main statement coming after it seem surprising, unlikely, or unexpected ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which do you like better, milk or tea? \" ___\"",
      "a": "Milk and tea",
      "b": "Yes, milk",
      "c": "Milk",
      "d": "Milk is better",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Or: Introduce two possible things to choose",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hard _________ she tried, she could not pass the test.",
      "a": "when",
      "b": "as",
      "c": "while",
      "d": "that",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- As...as: use in positive form or adjective (means \"equal\")",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "She hadn't reached the top of the stairs ___ he caught her round the waist.",
      "a": "because",
      "b": "if",
      "c": "although",
      "d": "before",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Before: earlier than a particular event or action ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ it rains, what shall we do?",
      "a": "Supposing",
      "b": "Imagining",
      "c": "Considering",
      "d": "Thinking",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Suppose: used to say you think something is true, although you are uncertain about it [= I guess]",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The dense fog will have cleared away ___ day breaks.",
      "a": "by the time",
      "b": "till the time",
      "c": "even if",
      "d": "though",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- By the Time: Indicating a future completion time (often used with future perfect)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}